121doc.co.uk 2016-11-11

# Privacy | How To Buy | 121Doc UK

This Website is owned and operated by Hexpress Healthcare Ltd ('we', 'us', 'our') trading as www.121doc.com/en to users and visitors ('you', 'your'). We take your privacy very seriously, and we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy, and to using technology to enhance your online security. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy ('the Policy') carefully as it contains important information about how we will use your personal data.

For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, Hexpress Healthcare Ltd is the 'data controller' (the company which is responsible for and controls the processing of your personal data).

## Personal data we may collect about you

Before you use certain areas of this Website, we ask you to register on it by requiring you to enter your personal information, including 'sensitive personal data' as defined by the Data Protection Act I998 ('the Act').

We will obtain personal data about you (such as your name, address, opinions and medical details whenever you complete an online medical questionnaire or any other online form. For example, we will obtain your personal data when you register to use this Website, complete the online questionnaire, send us feedback, post material, contact us for any reason, sign up to a service, and purchase goods or services. We may also obtain sensitive personal data about you if you volunteer it during the completion of an online form. If you volunteer such information, you will be consenting to our processing it for the purpose of obtaining a medical opinion and purchasing the treatment.

We may monitor your use of this Website through the use of cookies and similar tracking devices. For example, we may monitor how many times you visit, which pages you go to, traffic data, location data and the originating domain name of a user's internet service provider. This information helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this data will be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually. For further information on our use of cookies, please see our Cookie Policy. Occasionally we may receive information about you from other sources (such as credit reference agencies), which we will add to the information we already hold about you in order to help us personalise our service to you.

## How we use your personal data

We will use your personal data for the following purposes:

  * Administration.
  * Security vetting.
  * Improving our services.
  * Billing and order fulfilment.
  * Fraud prevention and detection.
  * Marketing—see 'Marketing and opting out', below.
  * Research, statistical analysis and behavioural analysis.
  * To help us identify you and any accounts you hold with us.
  * Customer profiling and analysing your purchasing preferences.
  * Credit scoring and credit checking—see 'Credit checking', below.
  * Customising this Website and its content to your particular preferences.
  * To notify you of any changes to this Website or to our services that may affect you.

## Marketing and opting out

If you have given permission, we may contact you by mail, email, telephone, SMS, text/picture/video message, fax, about our service, products, promotions, offers, charitable causes that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive any direct marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time. See further 'Your rights', below.

If you have given permission, we may share your personal data with organisations who are our business partners and we or they may contact you (unless you have asked us or them not to do so) by mail, email, telephone, SMS, text/picture/video message, fax, about our service, products, promotions, offers, charitable causes that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive any further direct marketing communications from us or from our business partners, you can opt out at any time. See further 'Your rights', below.

We will only contact you by mail, email, telephone, SMS, text/picture/video message, fax, about our service, products, promotions or offers if you have asked us to do so. If you have changed your mind and would prefer us not to contact you, then you can opt out at any time. See further 'Your rights', below.

## Disclosure of your personal data

**We may disclose your personal data to:**

  * Our agents and service providers.
  * Other companies within our group.
  * Credit reference agents—see 'Credit checking', below.
  * Our business partners in accordance with the 'Marketing and opting out' section above.
  * Law enforcement agencies in connection with any investigation to help prevent unlawful activity.

## Keeping your data secure

We will use technical and organisational measures to safeguard your personal data, for example:

  * Your data is stored on secure servers.
  * Payment details are encrypted using SSL technology.
  * Access to your account is controlled by a password and username that are unique to you.

While we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard your personal data, you acknowledge that the use of the internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal data that are transferred from you or to you via the internet.

## Monitoring

We may monitor and record communications with you such as telephone conversations and emails for the purpose of training, quality assurance, fraud prevention and compliance.

## Credit checking

To enable us and other companies in our group or partner companies to make credit decisions about you and for fraud prevention and money laundering purposes, we may search the files of credit reference and fraud prevention agencies (who will record the search). We may disclose information about how you conduct your account to such agencies and your information may be linked to records relating to other people living at the same address with whom you are financially linked. Other credit grantors may use this information to make credit decisions about you and the people with whom you are financially associated, as well as for fraud prevention, debtor tracing and money laundering purposes. If you provide false or inaccurate information and we suspect fraud, we will record this.

Information about other individuals

If you give us information on behalf of someone else, you confirm that the other person has appointed you to act on his/her behalf and has agreed that you can:

  * Receive on his/her behalf any data protection notices.
  * Give consent to the transfer of his/her personal data abroad.
  * Give consent on his/her behalf to the processing of his/her personal data.
  * Give consent to the processing of his/her sensitive personal data such as health information.

## Transfers of data out of the EEA

We may need to transfer your personal data to countries located outside the European Economic Area, for the purpose of fulfilling our obligations and providing our service. Any transfer of your data will be subject to a European Commission approved contract that will safeguard your privacy rights and give you remedies in the unlikely event of a security breach.

When you registered with this Website, you agreed that we may transfer your personal data to countries outside the European Economic Area. Rest assured that we will always ensure any transfer is subject to appropriate security measures to safeguard your personal data.

## Your rights

You have the right, subject to the payment of a small fee (£10), to request access to personal data that we may process about you. If you wish to exercise this right, you should:

  * Put your request in writing.
  * Attach a cheque in the amount of £10 made payable to us.
  * Specify the personal data you want access to, including any account or reference numbers where applicable.
  * Include proof of your identity and address (for instance, a copy of your driving licence or passport, and a recent utility or credit card bill).

You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. If you wish to exercise this right, you should:

  * Put your request in writing.
  * Specify the information that is incorrect and what it should be replaced with.
  * Provide us with enough information to identify you (for instance, your account number, username, registration details).

You also have the right to ask us to stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. If you wish to exercise this right, you should:

  * Put your request in writing.
  * Provide us with enough information to identify you (for instance, your account number, username, registration details).
  * If your objection is not to direct marketing in general, but to direct marketing by a particular channel (for instance, email or telephone), please specify the channel you are objecting to.

We welcome your feedback and questions. If you wish to contact us, please send an email to [patient-services@121doc.com](mailto:patient-services@121doc.com), or you can write to our registered office at 144 Mitcham Road, Tooting, London, SW17 9NH or call us on 020 3322 1430.

We may change this Policy from time to time. You should check this Policy occasionally to ensure you are aware of the most recent version that will apply each time you access this Website.
